immonitor.com 2017-04-18

# Privacy Policy - IMMonitor

Support  

**Our Privacy Policy**

**Your Information**  
IMMonitor Software does not gather any personally identifiable data such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address from users of this web site without previous notification.  
When purchasing our product, additional information is needed to fill your order. Any information provided by you will not be sold or given to anyone, and it will only be used by IMMonitor Software for filling your order and notifying you by email of updates.

**Cookies and Other Browser Information**  
IMMonitor Software's website utilizes visitor log files or cookies as well as hosted tracking with our website. The information collected with visitor cookies and through the hosted tracking is used to gain a better understanding of which sections of our site are most important to our users as well as identify possible navigation issues. This allows us to enhance your user experience in the future. The data collected from these visitor cookies and hosted tracking does not collect any personally identifiable information and is used in aggregate form only.

**Protect the information you give us**  
Where personal information is required, IMMonitor Software website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to transmit this data. This is done to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of the information you have offered. While IMMonitor Software strives to protect the personal information you submit to us, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure.   
IMMonitor Software will take reasonable steps necessary to protect the information you provide to us. We continually review our security procedures and mechanisms to ensure that adequate protections are in place. 

##### Our Products

Yahoo Messenger Monitor

Yahoo Messenger Monitor Sniffer - Monitor Yahoo Messenger conversations on network computers

MSN Messenger Monitor Sniffer

MSN Messenger Monitor Sniffer - Monitor MSN Messenger conversations on network computers

AIM Monitor Sniffer

AIM Monitor Sniffer - Monitor AIM conversations on network computers

ICQ Monitor Sniffer

ICQ Monitor Sniffer - Monitor ICQ Messenger conversations on network computers

MySpaceIM Monitor Sniffer

MySpaceIM Monitor Sniffer - Monitor MySpaceIM  conversations on network computers

IMMonitor Yahoo Messenger Spy

IMMonitor Yahoo Messenger Spy - Capture, sniff, and log Yahoo Messenger chat remotely within a LAN

IMMonitor MSN Spy

IMMonitor MSN Spy - Capture, sniff, and log MSN  Messenger chat remotely within a LAN

IMMonitor AIM Spy

IMMonitor AIM Spy - Capture, sniff, and log AIM chat remotely within a LAN

IMMonitor ICQ Spy

IMMonitor ICQ Spy - Capture, sniff, and log ICQ chat remotely within a LAN

IMMonitor MySpaceIM Spy

IMMonitor MySpaceIM Spy - Capture, sniff, and log MySpaceIM chat remotely within a LAN
